A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Virginia Secretary of Education, 1975-1997.
Library of Virginia
- Secretary's correspondence and subject files (Accession 32651), 1975-1985 (bulk 1982-1984)., Extent: 29 cubic feet (29 boxes)
  - American Management Systems, Inc., 1983. (Box 14)
  - American Society for Public Administration, 1982. (Box 14)
  - American Vocational Association, 1982-1984. (Box 14)
  - American Youth, 1984. (Box 14)
  - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, 1982. (Box 14)
  - Appalachia Center, 1984. (Box 14)
  - Appalachia Educational Laboratory, 1984. (Box 14)
  - Appalachia Regional Commission, 1982. (Box 14)
  - Appalachian Soil and Water Conservation Research Lab, 1984. (Box 14)
  - Appendix M, 1982-1984. (Box 14)
  - Appropriations Act, 1982. (Box 14)
  - Arms Control Association, 1983. (Box 14)
  - Arnold, Richard (AT and T), 1984. (Box 14)
  - Aspen Institute of Humanistic Studies, 1985. (Box 14)
  - Association for Preservation of Virginia Antiquities, 1984. (Box 14)
  - Association of Public School Administrators, 1983. (Box 14)
  - Association for Retarded Citizens - Virginia, 1982-1985. (Box 14)
  - Association for Supervision and Curriculum Development, 1985. (Box 14)
  - Association of Teacher Educators in Virginia, 1982. (Box 14)
  - Attorney General - Charles City County, 1982-1984. (Box 14)
  - Attorney General - Charlottesville, 1984. (Box 14)
  - Attorney General - Basic Aid, undated. (Box 14)
  - Attorney General, 1983. (Box 14)
  - Attorney General, 1982. (Box 15)
  - AGB National Trustee Workshop, 1983. (Box 15)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1982. (Box 15)
  - Averett College, 1982. (Box 15)
  - Aviation, Dept. of, 1982. (Box 15)
  - B - Miscellaneous, 1982. (Box 15)
  - Barefoot, Julia (Bedford County Public Schools), 1984. (Box 15)
  - Baltimore, University of, 1984. (Box 15)
  - Bank Street College of Education, 1984. (Box 15)
  - Binghamton University, 1984. (Box 15)
  - Biracial Committee Visitation - Radford University, 1981 May 8. (Box 15)
  - Riracial Committee Visitation - Virginia State University, 1981 May 6. (Box 15)
  - Biracial Committee meeting, 1980 Dec 18. (Box 15)
  - Biracial Advisory Committee under Wade Gilley, 1978-1981. (Box 15)
  - Blacksburg, Greater, Chamber of Commerce, 1983. (Box 15)
  - Block Grants Advisory Committee, 1982. (Box 15)
  - Bluefield College, 1982-1983. (Box 15)
  - Blue Ridge University, 1982-1983. (Box 15)
  - Blue Ridge School, 1982. (Box 15)
  - Bob Jones University, 1982-1983. (Box 15)
  - Boy's Home, 1982-1984. (Box 15)
  - Bryant, William, 1983-1984. (Box 15)
  - Burroughs Corp., 1983. (Box 15)
  - Business Education Partnerships, 1984. (Box 15)
  - C- Miscellaneous, 1982. (Box 15)
  - Campbell, Archibald, A., 1983. (Box 15)
  - Canada, 1984. (Box 15)
  - Capitol Cips, 1982. (Box 15)
  - Capitol Consortium for Library Resources, 1984. (Box 15)
  - Capital Outlay Projects, 1983-1984. (Box 15)
  - Capital Outlay Quarterly Reports, 1984 Apr-Oct. (Box 15)
  - Capital Outlay requests, 1983-1984. (Box 15)
  - Car Pool Committee, 1982. (Box 15)
  - Carry Forward Balances, 1983. (Box 15)
  - Carter, Cecil F., 1985. (Box 15)
  - CASE, 1982. (Box 15)
  - CASE - Jefferson Award Medal, 1982. (Box 15)
  - CAUSE for Positive Educationb, 1982. (Box 15)
  - Center on National Labor Policy, Inc., 1982. (Box 15)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1982. (Box 16)
  - Chambers of Commerce, Area, 1983. (Box 16)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Hialeah, FL, 1984. (Box 16)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Lynchburg, 1983. (Box 16)
  - CBN University, 1982. (Box 16)
  - Central Garage, 1982. (Box 16)
  - Character II, 1984. (Box 16)
  - Chatham Hall, 1982. (Box 16)
  - Cherokee County Board of Education (Georgia), 1982. (Box 16)
  - Chesapeake Bay Management Plan, 1983. (Box 16)
  - St. Christopher's School, 1982. (Box 16)
  - Cities in Schools, 1984. (Box 16)
  - CIT, 1983. (Box 16)
  - CIT materials, 1983. (Box 16)
  - CIT materials, 1982. (Box 16)
  - CIT reports, 1983. (Box 16)
  - CIT Subcommittee, 1983. (Box 16)
  - CIT - UVA Project examples, 1983. (Box 16)
  - Cincinnati, University of, 1982. (Box 16)
  - Civilian Club, 1982. (Box 16)
  - CLW - Community Learning Week, 1983-1984. (Box 16)
  - Coal and Energy Commission, 1982-1983. (Box 16)
  - Coalition of Concerned Citizens, 1984. (Box 16)
  - Cochrane, Harwood, 1983. (Box 16)
  - College and University Personnel Director's Conference, 1984. (Box 16)
  - Collegiate Schools, 1982. (Box 16)
  - Commencement Date, 1983. (Box 16)
  - Combat Drunk Driving, Task Force to, 1982. (Box 16)
  - Commerce, Dept. of, 1982. (Box 16)
  - Commonwealth Conference on Education, 1983-1985. (Box 16)
  - Comptroller's Office, 1983-1985. (Box 16)
  - Computer Services, Dept. of, 1982-1985. (Box 17)
  - Commission on Block Grants, Governor's, 1982-1983. (Box 17)
  - Critical Reevaluation, Conference on, 1983 Sept 23. (Box 17)
  - Critical Reevaluation, Conference on, 1983. (Box 17)
  - Critical Reevaluation Questions - JTC response, 1983. (Box 17)
  - Conference on Funding Higher Education in the 1990s, 1984. (Box 17)
  - Consolidation of Office Space, 1983. (Box 17)
  - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education in Northern Virginia, 1982. (Box 17)
  - Consortium for Professional Psychology, 1982-1984. (Box 17)
  - Consultant form (outside Virginia), 1982. (Box 17)
  - Cooperative Education, 1982-1983. (Box 17)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1985 Mar. (Box 17)
  - Council on Basic Education, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
  - Council on Black American Affairs, 1982. (Box 17)
  - Council for Children, 1984. (Box 17)
  - Council on Educational Facility Planners International, 1982. (Box 17)
  - Council on the Environment, 1982-1983. (Box 17)
  - Council of Independent Colleges in Virginia, 1982. (Box 17)
  - Council of Vice Presidents, 1982. (Box 17)
  - Council of Visitors, 1982. (Box 17)
  - D - Miscellaneous, 1982. (Box 17)
  - Date Care, 1982. (Box 17)
  - Davis, Richard J., 1982-1984. (Box 17)
  - Doherty, James, 1982. (Box 17)
  - Due Date Monitoring Reports - Memos, 1984. (Box 17)
  - E - Miscellaneous, 1982. (Box 17)
  - EEO Office, 1982. (Box 17)
  - Eastern Association of College and University Business Officers, 1983. (Box 17)
  - Eastern State Hospital, 1983. (Box 17)
  - Eastern Virginia Medical Authority, 1982-1983. (Box 17)
  - Eastern Virginia Writing Project, 1982. (Box 17)
  - Economic Development Proposals, 1983. (Box 17)
  - Economic Development - Peer Group, 1983. (Box 17)
  - Education Development Center, 1982. (Box 17)
  - Eminent Scholars, 1982. (Box 17)
  - Employee Relations Counselors, 1982. (Box 17)
  - Employment Reports, 1984. (Box 18)
  - Employment Reports, 1982-1984. (Box 18)
  - Engineering and Buildings, Division of, 1982. (Box 18)
  - Executive Agreements, 1983-1984. (Box 18)
  - Executie Orders, 1984. (Box 18)
  - Exemptions to Executive Orders, 1981-1982. (Box 18)
  - Faculty Senate of Virginia, 1983. (Box 18)
  - Fauntleroy, Hermanze, 1982-1984. (Box 18)
  - Federal Priorities, 1983. (Box 18)
  - Federal Priorities, 1982. (Box 18)
  - Ferrum College, 1982. (Box 18)
  - Financial Executive Institute, 1983. (Box 18)
  - Financial Statements, 1985. (Box 18)
  - Fine and Performing Arts, 1982. (Box 18)
  - Fire Safety, 1982. (Box 18)
  - Fishery Management Council, 1982. (Box 18)
  - Fishkin, Christine M. B., 1982. (Box 18)
  - Five Percent (5%) Reductions, 1982. (Box 18)
  - Foreign Exchange Students, 1983. (Box 19)
  - Foreign Service Institute, 1984. (Box 19)
  - Foreign Trade Institute, 1982-1983. (Box 19)
  - Fredericksburg, City of, 1983. (Box 19)
  - Freedom of Information Act, 1982. (Box 19)
  - Friends of Public Education, 1982. (Box 19)
  - Futterman, Sanford, 1982-1983. (Box 19)
  - Futures Commission, 1983. (Box 19)
  - G - Miscellaneous, 1982. (Box 19)
  - General Electric, 1984. (Box 19)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 1982-1984. (Box 19)
  - General Services, Dept. of - Dept. of Risk Management, 1982-1985. (Box 19)
  - General Services, Dept. of - Division of Purchase and Supply, 1981-1984. (Box 19)
  - Georgia, 1982. (Box 19)
  - Georgia, Univerity of, 1984. (Box 19)
  - Giroux, Henry - Article, 1984. (Box 19)
  - Godwin, Mills R., Jr., 1982. (Box 19)
  - Governor's Commission on Block Grants, 1982. (Box 19)
  - Governor's Conference on Small Business (3rd), 1984. (Box 19)
  - Governor's Training and Employment Council, 1984. (Box 19)
  - Governor's Job Training Coordinating Council, 1983-1985. (Box 19)
  - Governor's Regional Schools for Experimental Programs on Science and Technology, 1983. (Box 19)
  - Governor's School for the Arts in Southwest Virginia, 1985. (Box 19)
  - Governor's School for Regional Fine Arts, 1983. (Box 19)
  - Governor's School for the Gifted, 1982. (Box 19)
  - The Graduate Group, 1983-1984. (Box 19)
  - Gray, Joseph, 1983. (Box 19)
  - Guaranteed Student Loan, 1982. (Box 19)
  - H - Miscellaneous, 1982. (Box 19)
  - Hampton Institute, 1982-1983. (Box 19)
  - Hampton Roads Academy Community Association, 1982. (Box 19)
  - Hampton Roads Cultural Action Plan, 1982-1983. (Box 19)
  - Future of Hampton Roads, Inc., 1983. (Box 19)
  - Hampden Sydney, 1983. (Box 19)
  - Handicapped Children in Residential Facilities, 1982. (Box 19)
  - Handicapped Persons, Overall Advisory Council on Needs of, 1982. (Box 19)
  - Health, Dept. of, 1983-1984. (Box 19)
  - Hershman, James H., Jr., 1982. (Box 19)
  - Higher Education Institutions Bonds - Series B, 1982. (Box 19)
  - Higher Education and Public Policy Program, 1985. (Box 19)
  - High Technology, 1983-1984. (Box 19)
  - Highways and Transportation, 1983-1984. (Box 19)
  - Hollins College, 1982. (Box 19)
  - Holloway, Chuck, 1984. (Box 19)
  - Housing and Community Development, 1982-1983. (Box 19)
  - IBM, 1982-1984. (Box 19)
  - IEEE Impact, 1984. (Box 19)
  - Illinois, 1982. (Box 19)
  - Independent School Teachers Association, 1984. (Box 19)
  - Industrial Development, Division of, 1981-1983. (Box 19)
  - Information Technology, Dept. of, 1984. (Box 19)
  - Institute on International Trade, 1982. (Box 19)
  - Integrated Computer Systems, 1982. (Box 19)
  - Intergovernmental Advisory Council on Education, 1984. (Box 20)
  - Intergovernmental Review Process, 1983. (Box 20)
  - International Baccalaureate Program, 1982-1983. (Box 20)
  - International Trade Institute, 1983. (Box 20)
  - Interns, 1982-1983. (Box 20)
  - Invoices, 1985 Jan-July. (Box 20)
  - Jefferson Foundation, 1984. (Box 20)
  - Job Opportunity, 1982. (Box 20)
  - Job Training Coordinating Council, 1982. (Box 20)
  - Job Training Partnership Act, 1982. (Box 20)
  - Jobs for Virginia Graduates, 1982. (Box 20)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 1984. (Box 20)
  - Johnson, Walkley, 1982-1983. (Box 20)
  - Johnson, William R., 1983. (Box 20)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 1982-1984. (Box 20)
  - Junior League of Charlottesville, 1982-1983. (Box 20)
  - K - Miscellaneous, 1982. (Box 20)
  - Keep Virginia Beautiful, 1982. (Box 20)
  - Kennedy School, 1982. (Box 20)
  - King, Martin Luther, 1982. (Box 20)
  - Kiwanis Club, 1982. (Box 20)
  - Knapp, John L., 1984. (Box 20)
  - Labor, Dept. of, 1983-1985. (Box 20)
  - Leadership, Metro Richmond, 1983-1984. (Box 20)
  - League of Women Voters, 1982. (Box 20)
  - Legislative Implementation Report, 1982. (Box 20)
  - Lemmon, W. L., 1982. (Box 20)
  - Leppard, David, 1984. (Box 20)
  - Lemke, Randy, 1983. (Box 20)
  - Library of America, 1984. (Box 20)
  - Libing Library, 1982. (Box 20)
  - Literacy Commission, 1983. (Box 20)
  - Literacy Fund, 1982-1984. (Box 20)
  - Local Government Advisory Council, 1981-1983. (Box 20)
  - Local Government Officials Conference, 1984. (Box 20)
  - Louisa Lions Club Charter meeting, 1984. (Box 20)
  - Lynchburg Collge, 1982. (Box 20)
  - Lynchburg Forum, 1984. (Box 20)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development, 1982-1984. (Box 20)
  - Maryand Leadership Conference, 1983. (Box 20)
  - Maryland, University of, 1984. (Box 20)
  - Massanutten Vocational Technical Center, 1982-1984. (Box 20)
  - Memorandum: Agency Head, Presidents of Colleges and Universities, Rectors, 1982-1984. (Box 20)
  - Memorandum of Understanding, 1982-1983. (Box 21)
  - Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1982-1983. (Box 21)
  - Mesinger, John F., 1982. (Box 21)
  - Metro Chamber Forum, 1983. (Box 21)
  - Miller School of Albemarle, 1982. (Box 21)
  - Minority Business Reports, 1984. (Box 21)
  - Minority Students Preparatory Program, 1982. (Box 21)
  - John Motley Morehead Foundation, 1984. (Box 21)
  - Moton Development Endowment Programs, 1982. (Box 21)
  - National Academy of Education, 1984. (Box 21)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1982-1984. (Box 21)
  - National Association of College Admissions Counselors, 1982-1983. (Box 21)
  - National Association of Principals and Schools for Girls, 1982-1983. (Box 21)
  - National Association of Secondary School Principals, 1982-1984. (Box 21)
  - National Association of State Boards of Education, 1984. (Box 21)
  - National Association of Teachers Agencies, 1984. (Box 21)
  - National Business College, 1983. (Box 21)
  - National Commission on Excellence in Education, 1983. (Box 21)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures, 1983. (Box 21)
  - National Education Association, 1982-1984. (Box 21)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1983. (Box 21)
  - National Federation of State Humanities Councils, 1982. (Box 21)
  - National Foundation for the Advancement of the Arta, 1982. (Box 21)
  - National Humanities Center, 1983. (Box 21)
  - National Issues and Trends in Higher Education, 1984. (Box 21)
  - National PTA, 1984. (Box 21)
  - National Science Resources Center, 1984. (Box 21)
  - National Spelling Bee, 1985. (Box 21)
  - National Student Parent Mock Election, 1984. (Box 21)
  - National School Board Association, 1984. (Box 21)
  - National School Boards Association, 1984. (Box 21)
  - National Scholarship Service and Fund for Negro Students of the S. E. Regional Office, 1983. (Box 21)
  - National Science Board, 1982-1983. (Box 21)
  - NCHEMS - National Assembly, 1983. (Box 21)
  - New England Board of Higher Education, 1984. (Box 21)
  - News articles, 1982-1985. (Box 21)
  - New York State Education Dept., 1982. (Box 21)
  - National Governors Association - General, 1982-1984. (Box 21)
  - National Governors Association - Annual meeting, 1985. (Box 21)
  - National Governors Association - Center for Policy Research, 1984. (Box 21)
  - National Governors Association - Committee on Human Resources, 1984. (Box 21)
  - National Governors Association - Education Aides, 1985. (Box 21)
  - National Governors Association - Education for Economic Security, 1983. (Box 21)
  - National Governors Association - Education Plan, 1985. (Box 21)
  - National Governors Association - Education Subcommittee, 1984-1985. (Box 21)
  - National Governors Association - Education Subcommittee, 1985. (Box 22)
  - National Governors Association - Education Subcommittee - Staff Advisory Committee, 1985. (Box 22)
  - National Governors Association - Federal Budget, 1982-1983. (Box 22)
  - National Governors Association - Issues in Federal-State Relations, 1982. (Box 22)
  - National Governors Association - JTC Testimony on Higher Education Reauthorization, 1985. (Box 22)
  - National Governors Association - Math and Science / Engineering and Science Technology Innovations, 1982-1983. (Box 22)
  - National Governors Association - Memos to the Cabinet, 1982-1983. (Box 22)
  - National Governors Association - Mid-Winter Meeting, 1985 Feb. (Box 22)
  - National Governors Association - Paper on Student Finance Aid, 1985. (Box 22)
  - National Governors Association - Policy Resolutions, 1985. (Box 22)
  - National Governors Association - Subcommittee meeting, 1985 Apr. (Box 22)
  - National Governors Association - Subcommittee on Teachers, 1985. (Box 22)
  - NIE, 1984. (Box 22)
  - Non-State Agencies, 1984. (Box 22)
  - Norfolk Academy, 1983-1984. (Box 22)
  - Norfolk, City Mayor of, 1983-1984. (Box 22)
  - Norfolk Naval Shipyard, 1982. (Box 22)
  - North Carolina Commission on Education for Economic Growth, 1984. (Box 22)
  - North Carolina Community College System, 1983. (Box 22)
  - North Carolina Governor's Office, 83 19. (Box 22)
  - North Carolina State University, 1980-1983. (Box 22)
  - Oceanic Educational Foundation, 1980-1984. (Box 22)
  - Office Budget, 1982. (Box 22)
  - Office of Employee Relations Counselors, 1984. (Box 22)
  - Organization Membership List, 1982-1983. (Box 22)
  - Orientation of New Board Members, 1982-1983. (Box 22)
  - Personnel and Training, 1981-1985. (Box 22)
  - Personnel and Training - EEO, 1981-1983. (Box 22)
  - Personnel and Training - Missed Opportunity Report, 1984. (Box 23)
  - Phi Delta Kappa, 1983-1985. (Box 23)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1983-1984. (Box 23)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of - Office Budget, 1983. (Box 23)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of - Stuart Connock, 1984. (Box 23)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of - Stuart Connock, 1983. (Box 23)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of - Education Section, Herb Hunt, 1983. (Box 23)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of - Federal Assistance Award data, 1983. (Box 23)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of - Bill Hill, 1984. (Box 23)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of - Non-General Fund Balance, 1984. (Box 23)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of - Division of Research, Evaluation and Policy, 1983. (Box 23)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of - William Rowland, 1984. (Box 23)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of - Nancy Suttenfield, 1984-1985. (Box 23)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of - Education Operating Budget, 1984-1986. (Box 23)
  - Policy Advisory Commission on High Technology, 1984. (Box 23)
  - Politics in Higher Education, 1982-1983. (Box 23)
  - Potomac and Chesapeake Chapter, Association of College Admission Counselors, 1982-1983. (Box 23)
  - Presidential Scholars, 1983-1984. (Box 24)
  - Price Waterhouse and Co., 1982. (Box 24)
  - Project Discovery, 1983-1984. (Box 24)
  - Project Discovery - Meetings, 1983-1984. (Box 24)
  - Psychiatric Associates of Tidewater, 1982. (Box 24)
  - Public Law 94-142, undated. (Box 24)
  - Public Television, 1982-1984. (Box 24)
  - Purdue University, 1983. (Box 24)
  - Randolph Macon College - Ashland, 1984. (Box 24)
  - Randolph Macon Women's College, 1983. (Box 24)
  - Reorganization Proposals, 1983. (Box 24)
  - Reorganization Proposals, 1983. (Box 24)
  - Regulatory Reform, 1982. (Box 24)
  - Regulation Review Summary, 1984. (Box 24)
  - Requests for Funding Programs, 1983. (Box 24)
  - Research and Teaching Institute, 1982. (Box 24)
  - Research Triangle, 1984. (Box 24)
  - Responses to Mr. Coleman - Richmond Times Dispatch, 1984. (Box 24)
  - Resumes, 1982-1985. (Box 24)
  - Retention Studies, 1982-1984. (Box 24)
  - Richmond Community High School, 1982-1983. (Box 24)
  - Richmond Urban Forum, 1983. (Box 24)
  - Richmond Times Dispatch, 1982. (Box 24)
  - Admiral Rickover Foundation, 1983-1985. (Box 24)
  - Roanoke Times and World News, 1982. (Box 24)
  - Roanoke Valley Educational Consortium, 1982. (Box 24)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1982. (Box 24)
  - Sorbornie, Dr. Edward J., 1982. (Box 24)
  - Salary benchmarks, 1983. (Box 24)
  - Salary Incentive Fund, 1982. (Box 24)
  - Salary Study DOE and VEA, 1982. (Box 24)
  - Savings Bonds Participants, 1982-1984. (Box 24)
  - School / Business Partnerships High Schools, 1984. (Box 24)
  - School for Contemporary Education, 1982. (Box 24)
  - Science and Technology Policy Advisory Commission, 1984. (Box 24)
  - Science and Technology Policy Advisory Commission - Meeting, 1984 Sept. (Box 24)
  - Science and Technology Policy Advisory Commission, 1982-1983. (Box 24)
  - Science and Technology Policy Advisory Commission - Responses, 1983-1984. (Box 24)
  - Science and Technology Task Force, 1983. (Box 24)
  - Science and Technology Task Force - Meeting, 1983 July. (Box 24)
  - Science and Technology Implementation Comm., 1983. (Box 24)
  - Secretarial Directives Study, 1984. (Box 24)
  - Seemiller, Bonnie, 1982-1983. (Box 24)
  - SELMA, 1982. (Box 24)
  - Senior Citizens Higher Education Act, 1982. (Box 24)
  - Seven Hills School, 1984. (Box 24)
  - Shaffer, Paul, 1982-1983. (Box 24)
  - Shaky State Budgets, 1982. (Box 24)
  - Shenandoah College and Conservatory of Music, 1983-1984. (Box 24)
  - State Higher Education Executive Officers Association (SHEEO), 1982-1983. (Box 24)
  - Shuford, Paul M., 82-1983. (Box 24)
  - Silbur, John, 1982-1983. (Box 24)
  - Simon Concept Paper on Higher Education Reauthorization, undated. (Box 24)
  - Simon's Rock of Bard College, 1984. (Box 24)
  - Sizer, Theodore, 1982-1983. (Box 24)
  - Small Business, High Technology Institute, 1983. (Box 24)
  - Small and Minority Business, 1982. (Box 25)
  - Smith, Roy, 1983. (Box 25)
  - Snelling, Barbara W., 1984. (Box 25)
  - Software Engineering Institute, 1984. (Box 25)
  - Sonoma State University, 1985. (Box 25)
  - Social Services, Dept. of, 1982-1984. (Box 25)
  - Southeatern Tidewater Opportunities, 1983. (Box 25)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1982. (Box 25)
  - Southern Center for International Studies, 1982-1984. (Box 25)
  - Southern Christian Leadership, 1983. (Box 25)
  - Southern Governor's Association, 1982. (Box 25)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board, 1982-1984. (Box 25)
  - Southern Regional Conference on Involvement and Learning, 1985. (Box 25)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1983. (Box 25)
  - Special Commission on Education, 1983. (Box 25)
  - Spring Hill Center, 1982-1983. (Box 25)
  - Southern Regional Education Board - Meeting, 1983 June. (Box 25)
  - Southern Regional Education Board - Career Ladders Clearinghouse, 1984-1985. (Box 25)
  - Southern Regional Education Board - Commission on Health and Human Services, undated. (Box 25)
  - Southern Regional Education Board - Educational Progress, 1984. (Box 25)
  - Southern Regional Education Board - Executive Committee meetings, 1983. (Box 25)
  - Southern Regional Education Board - Executive Commitee meetings, 1982. (Box 25)
  - Southern Regional Education Board - JTC Paper, 1985 May. (Box 25)
  - Southern Regional Education Board - Legislative Work Conference, 1983. (Box 25)
  - Southern Regional Education Board - Legislative Work Conference, 1982. (Box 25)
  - Southern Regional Education Board - Financing meeting, 1984. (Box 25)
  - Southern Regional Education Board - Taks Force on Higher Education, 1982. (Box 25)
  - Southern Regional Education Board - Teacher Accreditation, 1984. (Box 25)
  - St. Anne's Belfield School, 1984. (Box 25)
  - State Education Policy Consortium meeting, 1984. (Box 25)
  - State Fair, 1983-1984. (Box 25)
  - State Government News, 1982-1983. (Box 25)
  - State Government Research and Development Activities, 1984. (Box 25)
  - State Police, Dept. of, 1982. (Box 26)
  - New York State University at Binghamton, 1981-1983. (Box 26)
  - State Water Control Board, undated. (Box 26)
  - Stepka, Bill, 1982-1984. (Box 26)
  - Steward School, 1982-1983. (Box 26)
  - Stuart Hall, 1982-1985. (Box 26)
  - Student Achievement, 1984. (Box 26)
  - Student Legislator Forum, 1982-1983. (Box 26)
  - Stumm, Thomas W., 1983. (Box 26)
  - Southeastern Universities Research Association, 1984. (Box 26)
  - Southeastern Universities Research Association, 1983 May. (Box 26)
  - Southeastern Universities Research Association, 1983 Jan-Apr. (Box 26)
  - Southeastern Universities Research Association, 1982 May-Nov. (Box 26)
  - Southeastern Universities Research Association, 1983 June. (Box 26)
  - Southeastern Universities Research Association, 1983 July. (Box 26)
  - Southeastern Universities Research Association / Continuous Electron Beam Accelerator Facility, 1984. (Box 26)
  - Southeastern Universities Research Association / Continuous Electron Beam Accelerator Facility, 1983 Aug-Dec. (Box 26)